[
	{
		"question": "The chicked crossed the road to get to the other side",
		"category": "Entertainment",
		"subcategory": "Non Sense",
		"answer": true
	},
	{
		"question": "The chicked crossed the road to get to the other side",
		"category": "Entertainment",
		"subcategory": "Non Sense",
		"answer": false
	},
	{
		"question": "The chicked crossed the road to get to the other side",
		"category": "Entertainment",
		"subcategory": "Non Sense",
		"answer": true
	},
	{
		"question": "The chicked crossed the road to get to the other side",
		"category": "Entertainment",
		"subcategory": "Non Sense",
		"answer": false
	},
	{
		"question": "The chicked crossed the road to get to the other side",
		"category": "Entertainment",
		"subcategory": "Non Sense",
		"answer": true
	},
	{
		"question": "The chicked crossed the road to get to the other side",
		"category": "Entertainment",
		"subcategory": "Non Sense",
		"answer": false
	},
	{
		"question": "The chicked crossed the road to get to the other side",
		"category": "Entertainment",
		"subcategory": "Non Sense",
		"answer": true
	},
	{
		"question": "The chicked crossed the road to get to the other side",
		"category": "Entertainment",
		"subcategory": "Non Sense",
		"answer": false
	},
	{
		"question": "The chicked crossed the road to get to the other side",
		"category": "Entertainment",
		"subcategory": "Non Sense",
		"answer": true
	},
	{
		"question": "The chicked crossed the road to get to the other side",
		"category": "Entertainment",
		"subcategory": "Non Sense",
		"answer": false
	}
]